

f https://www.fb.com/volodyakushnir

✓ volodymyr.kushnir@me.com

O volodymyr-kushnir

S volodymyr_kushnir
☐ +38 (095) 26 00 797

RÉSUMÉ

— Hello! I'm skilled frontend developer with 7 years of experience in UI/UX design, application development, and database modelling. I strive to craft precise, responsive, fast, easy-to-use environments with both strong purpose and great looks.

EXPERIENCE

24th January 2017 - present

Front End Developer at Binary Studio

- build, test, and deploy a frontend written with React + Redux
- do some extra things from time to time

1st October 2016 – 31st December 2016

Full Stack Developer at **Dutchstar**

• built, tested, and deployed applications written with React + Redux and Phalcon + MySQL

25th May 2014 – forever

Married (Lyudmyla Mandzyuk

• do all the different things

1st September 2012 – 30th September 2016

Service Center Databases Lead at <u>Sumitomo Electric Bordnetze</u> Ukraine

- managed MySQL multi-master clusters, Oracle failover clusters, Microsoft SQL mirrored/replicated servers (monitoring, backup/restore, users/groups/roles, schemas)
- built and benchmarked fast, efficient SQL queries
- optimized database engines, indexes, etc.
- crafted web dashboards, reports using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, SQL

1st September 2011 – 30th September 2016

IT production subdivision manager at <u>Sumitomo Electric</u> Bordnetze Ukraine

- designed computer-aided manufacturing processes
- interconnected different production systems' databases (push or pull data using replication, triggers, scheduled events, cron jobs)
- built high-availability systems, minimized downtime
- designed and built BDE (BetriebsDatenErfassung) data aggregator system designed to assist in planning, manufacturing, monitoring and controlling
- analyzed and transformed data
- wrote docs, manuals, guidelines, and memos

9th April 2008

Was officially hired (employee #943) by <u>Sumitomo Electric</u> <u>Bordnetze</u> Ukraine

(worked as a contractor previously)

LANGUAGES

UKRAINIAN RUSSIAN ENGLISH

SKILLS

HTML CSS JS PHP BOILERPLATE
BOOTSTRAP SEMANTIC UI LESS SASS
JQUERY ANGULARJS REACT LODASH
GRUNT GULP BOWER WEBPACK
NODEJS NPM MICROSOFT OFFICE
PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR DELPHI
VB VBA VBSCRIPT LINUX WINDOWS
MACOS MYSQL POSTGRESQL
MICROSOFT SQL DB2 CCNA ITIL

CHARACTER

EXPLORER STRAIGHTFORWARD
DEVOTED PEDANTIC AGNOSTIC
CONTENTIOUS PROCRASTINATOR
RELEVANT EMPATHETIC STORYTELLER
CONFIDENT CONSISTENT
CHALLENGING

LIKES 😃

HUMOUR PATIENCE DOGS MOVIES
AAPL FC BARCELONA JÄGERMEISTER
L'VIV FRISBEE MIDNIGHT BLUE
ELECTROPOP CUCINA ITALIANA '80S
SELF-EDUCATION DEMOCRACY
ATTENTION TO DETAILS GRAMMAR
SPELLCHECK SEMANTICS MINI-SERIES
RYAN GOSLING EMMA STONE
CURAPROX 5460 MEH

DISLIKES 😩

OWN BAD HABITS POLITICS RACISM ASS-KISSERS VODKA INCOMPETENCE ENVY GOLF • CHARTREUSE INSECTS METRO PREJUDICE REALITY-SHOWS JŪRMALA 14th February 2008 – 31st January 2011

Software engineer at Sumitomo Electric Bordnetze Ukraine

- designed UI and UX for native applications and web pages
- built simple apps to assist in manufacturing process using Delphi, VB, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL
- managed Microsoft SQL, MySQL, and Firebird databases

February 2006 - August 2007

Graphic designer at **Terminal**

- designed booklets, flyers, business cards, posters using Adobe CS (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign)
- managed inkjet plotters and printers
- built websites using Macromedia Dreamweaver, Macromedia Flash (ActionScript)

April 2004 - December 2004

System administrator at Pyramid

- managed a network of dozen Windows workstations and one Linux gateway (DHCP, DNS, proxy, ACLs)
- kept PCs health (install OS over PXE, backup/restore, antivirus, software updates, hardware upgrades etc.)

16th May 2003 – present

Got my internal passport (with a traditionally awkward photo, of course) — can't wait to replace it with a new Passport of the Citizen of Ukraine

••• couldn't do much really for the first few years...

6th October 1986

Born in Ternopil, Ukraine — Thanks, mom and dad!

EDUCATION

December 2005 – April 2006
Certificates of CCNA Course
Completion at Cisco Networking
Academy Program

1st September 2003 – 30th June 2008 Bachelor's degree in computer science at Ternopil National Technical University

1st September 1993 – 21st June 2003
Certificate of graduation at №20
Middle School of General
Education

1st October 1995 – 23rd May 1999 Certificate of graduation at Ternopil Art School for Children